[Music]
[音乐]
本教程是关于展开
this tutorial is about the unfurling
机制，这是一个非常不寻常的小
我从这本书中学到的机制
this tutorial is about the unfurling
mechanism it's a quite an unusual little
大卫·佩洛姆（David Pellom）真的叫乌鸦（Raven）
很棒但是很漂亮
mechanism it's a quite an unusual little
mechanism that I took from this book by
插图和非常聪明的弹出式窗口
我将贯穿整个过程，以便您看到
mechanism that I took from this book by
David Pellom called the Raven really
到底有多伟大
我将在下面解释展开机制
David Pellom called the Raven really
fantastic but really beautiful
最终这些是点差，所以这是
展开机制，这是一个
fantastic but really beautiful
illustration and very clever pop-ups so
我将在本教程中进行解释
然后这是本书的结尾
illustration and very clever pop-ups so
I'll just run through it so you can see
这是我认为的展开机制
理解它的最好方法是看
I'll just run through it so you can see
just how great it is really and then
从后面看，您会看到
整个事物由v形折叠驱动
just how great it is really and then
I'll explain the unfurling mechanism at
在这里，v形是
v折，v折上的角度
I'll explain the unfurling mechanism at
the end these are the spreads so this is
与页面上的角度相同
因此，当页面平坦时，v形折叠位于
the end these are the spreads so this is
the unfolding mechanism this is the one
平v形折叠向上并
有一块推向后
the unfolding mechanism this is the one
I'm going to explain in this tutorial
最容易向您展示的手指
我做了这个，所以我把它
I'm going to explain in this tutorial
and then this is the end of the book
在那里，这是V故障
这将是手的前面
and then this is the end of the book
this is the unfurling mechanism I think
是向上推手指的那一块
它在这里向后推，
this is the unfurling mechanism I think
the best way to understand it is to look
手指实际上是铰接在顶部
V形折叠的延伸部分
the best way to understand it is to look
at it from behind you'll see that the
打开和关闭，您可以看到
在书中工作而不是仅仅
at it from behind you'll see that the
whole thing is powered by a v-fold in
像我一样在这里变黄
做了一系列不同的
whole thing is powered by a v-fold in
here and the v-fold is the type of
不同手指的高度，如果
我们从侧面看它，这里有一个
here and the v-fold is the type of
v-fold where the angles on the v-fold
所有人都有很多不同的身高
不同的形状，但都被向上推
v-fold where the angles on the v-fold
are the same as the angles on the page
推动这一切的一切
这些不同的水平和一块
are the same as the angles on the page
so when the page is flat the v-fold lies
它所反对的是不同的
水平，所以当你看着它会
so when the page is flat the v-fold lies
flat the v-fold is extended up and
真的是黄色的东西
不同级别，还有红色
flat the v-fold is extended up and
there's a piece that pushes up the back
会有不同的水平，但我已经
只是说清楚一点，所以你
there's a piece that pushes up the back
of the fingers easiest to show you on
可以理解，所以我现在做一个
我已经把所有的东西都剪了
of the fingers easiest to show you on
this one that I've made so I'll put that
所以我会解释给他们看
很简单，这是基础表
this one that I've made so I'll put that
there so here it is this is the V fault
完全对折
这是这两个角度的V折
there so here it is this is the V fault
this would be the front of the hand this
45度增加了，我会的
现在就折一下，折起来
this would be the front of the hand this
is the piece that pushes up the fingers
你真的很认真地看着这个
可以看到它在
is the piece that pushes up the fingers
it pushes up at the back here and the
页面，以便将成为V
它会在页面顶部附近
it pushes up at the back here and the
the finger is actually hinged on the top
指向这样的东西
没错，所以我就把
the finger is actually hinged on the top
of this extension to the v-fold so as it
粘在那里，因为它是平坦的
弹出式窗口是扁平的，可以将两面都粘上
of this extension to the v-fold so as it
opens and closes you can see how that
与此同时
我将其放置在此处，确保
opens and closes you can see how that
works in the book rather than to just
弹出窗口的中央折痕对齐
与基地的中央折痕
works in the book rather than to just
being one flat level here yellow as I've
粘下来折叠起来只是为了使
确保一切顺利
being one flat level here yellow as I've
made there's a whole series of different
哦耶
所以现在你会看到这块黄色的
made there's a whole series of different
heights for the different fingers so if
粘在v形折叠的一侧，所以
这是我要添加的黄色部分
heights for the different fingers so if
we look at it sideways on here there's a
上，你会看到那黄色
件粘在v形折叠的一侧
we look at it sideways on here there's a
whole lot of different heights to all
所以这是一块那么低的黄色
黄片，将被粘上
whole lot of different heights to all
different shapes but all pushed up by
在V形折叠的这一侧，请确保
角落就在角落里，否则
different shapes but all pushed up by
the the piece that's pushing it has all
好吧，它显然不会关闭
正确地在这上面放一些胶水
the the piece that's pushing it has all
these different levels and the piece
这里的三角形那里胶太多
我待会儿干
these different levels and the piece
that it's pushing against has different
我将其关闭以确保其正常工作，
现在给第二分钟
that it's pushing against has different
levels so when you look at this it would
这是一块带有插槽的零件
那红色的碎片穿过
levels so when you look at this it would
be really the yellow piece would have
这将继续在这里插槽是
刚好高于这里的水平
be really the yellow piece would have
different levels and also the red piece
你可能会把它全部
一张卡，但我认为它也相当
different levels and also the red piece
would have different levels but I've
保持坚韧很好，这是几个
厚度，所以我已经标记了插槽
would have different levels but I've
just made one to make it clear so you
将与折痕平行
我刚刚把它切掉了
just made one to make it clear so you
can understand it so now I'll make one
好的
荡妇需要在顶部上方
can understand it so now I'll make one
I've cut out all the pieces in advance
边缘，我将其粘在上面
好吧，我将其关闭
I've cut out all the pieces in advance
so I'll explain them all they're all
确保一切正常，这显然是一个
假人，你可以看到它伸出
so I'll explain them all they're all
quite simple this is the base sheet
边缘，但没关系，这只是
解释机制，所以我们
quite simple this is the base sheet
folded in half folded really thoroughly
现在是那样移动吗红色
一块，这将推高
this is the V fold both these angles are
整个东西实际上就是
移动方式的机制
this is the V fold both these angles are
45 degrees I have increased it yes I'll
这是我做的地带
压下中间，我要粘
45 degrees I have increased it yes I'll
just crease that now so that crease
一分钟
但是首先我们要在其中一个
just crease that now so that crease
really thoroughly you look at this you
结束，所以我要在那儿剪一点
所以这将是一个选项卡
really thoroughly you look at this you
can see where it's positioned on the
现在将其粘贴到页面上
此时，您会看到在
can see where it's positioned on the
page so that piece is going to be the V
这本书的底部是红色的全部
制成一件，但由于
page so that piece is going to be the V
it'll be near the top of the page
测量和填充的并发症
我要用两块做成
it'll be near the top of the page
pointing down it something like this
这件，那件出现的
该高度必须与
pointing down it something like this
that's about right so I'll just put the
总黄色，因此现在已进入标签页
一方面，我只需要衡量
that's about right so I'll just put the
glue on there and as it's flat when the
高整个事情需要来这个
时间，所以我将其标记为
glue on there and as it's flat when the
pop-up is flat you can glue both sides
与底部齐平，这是
其他标签将是，所以我要
pop-up is flat you can glue both sides
at the same time
切成一个标签，然后切
那关
I'll position it on there make sure the
对，所以这将是另一个
现在，我可以将双方粘合在一起
I'll position it on there make sure the
central crease of the pop-up is
在一起只是为了使其真正强大
推杆我们去
central crease of the pop-up is
with the central crease of the base
刚干的时候你在这里看到
因为我用红色做成了
with the central crease of the base
stick it down fold it shut just to make
我放了两根铰链
黄色的顶部，这样您就可以
stick it down fold it shut just to make
sure that everything is working smoothly
附加所有这就是铰链
只是一小片，里面有折叠
sure that everything is working smoothly
oh yeah
中间需要与
插槽
oh yeah
so now you'll see that this yellow piece
在上面放一些胶水，那就是
要去那里好吧，我们要
so now you'll see that this yellow piece
is stuck to one side of the v-fold so
通过这个线程这将
坚持下去，它会上升
is stuck to one side of the v-fold so
here's the yellow piece I'm going to add
通过插槽并将其粘在
整个事情与
here's the yellow piece I'm going to add
on and you can see that that yellow
我戴上的铰链，所以我就放
该标签上的一些胶粘在那里
on and you can see that that yellow
piece is glued to one side of the v-fold
下来只是确保所有这些
工作得很好，我略有点击
piece is glued to one side of the v-fold
so here's the yellow piece that low
在那边，现在更直了
当他们底座平的时候
so here's the yellow piece that low
yellow piece and it's going to be glued
整个手指都是扁平的，所以我要
弄平这是我的作品
yellow piece and it's going to be glued
to this side of the v-fold make sure the
要添加它会坚持下去
到这个，让我们关闭它
to this side of the v-fold make sure the
corner is right in the corner otherwise
这将坚持在那里，我已经
只需将胶水放在两个标签上即可
corner is right in the corner otherwise
well it obviously won't won't close
一个应该指向的红军
这样，当您向其中添加手指时
well it obviously won't won't close
properly so put some glue on this
该条的结尾继续
躺下时起皱，您可以看到
properly so put some glue on this
triangle here bit too much glue there
太久了，这将
下来在这里，所以我要修剪一些
triangle here bit too much glue there
I'll just give it a moment to dry off
立即关闭然后折叠
这下来，你可以看到我
I'll just give it a moment to dry off
I'll close it make sure it's working and
实际上稍微离开那里，所以现在你
可以看到这是展开的
I'll close it make sure it's working and
give that a minute now the second piece
仍然有点长，倾向于陷入
页面有点，所以我可以切断
give that a minute now the second piece
this is a piece here with the slot in it
可能会有所帮助，所以这是
这是展开机制，
this is a piece here with the slot in it
that the red piece goes through so
如果你想用多个手指
像在手中，那么你可以使
that the red piece goes through so
that's going to go on here the slot is
黄色在许多不同的水平和
你可以做这件红色的
that's going to go on here the slot is
going to be just above the level here
推高许多不同的水平
这本书的另一个聪明之处是
going to be just above the level here
you could probably make it all out of
这个机制隐藏在David中
佩勒姆（Pelham）的设计，所以我只告诉你
you could probably make it all out of
one card but I think it's also quite
页面打开时他是如何做到的
你看到那只手实际上是
one card but I think it's also quite
good to keep it tough so it's several
拿着一个小盒盒，所以实际上
小盒挂在顶部
good to keep it tough so it's several
thicknesses so I've marked slots it's
黄色在这里，它上下滑动
这是单独的一块，所以如果我们举起
thicknesses so I've marked slots it's
going to be parallel with the crease at
那你会看到这件
拇指是一块，这是
going to be parallel with the crease at
the bottom I've just cut it out
另一个使小盒实际上隐藏起来
所以实际上有一件
okay
停留在这里即将到来
这里还有另外一块
okay
that needs to be just above the top
掉下来藏起来了
我会这样做，以便您了解如何
that needs to be just above the top
edge and I'll just glue that one on as
它是隐藏的，我会用
不同的颜色我会用一些
edge and I'll just glue that one on as
well right again I'll just close it make
绿色，所以我会做得非常
基本上是这样
well right again I'll just close it make
sure it all works this is obviously a
所以这会粘在红色上
那里放了一点胶
sure it all works this is obviously a
dummy you can see it sticking out of the
坚持在那里，现在那里
另一块重叠的绿色
dummy you can see it sticking out of the
edge but it doesn't matter it's just
有一块重叠的绿色
在那里，将隐藏
edge but it doesn't matter it's just
explaining the mechanisms so there we
机制真的只是放少量
胶水粘在上面
explaining the mechanisms so there we
are that's moving like that now the red
顶部的一块不错，这是
隐藏我需要投射的机制
are that's moving like that now the red
piece this is going to be pushing up the
向下，这样就足够了
顶部边缘，但足够短
piece this is going to be pushing up the
whole thing this is what actually makes
它不会坠入胡同
书中有
whole thing this is what actually makes
the mechanism moving the way it does so
显然，你知道这很聪明
这是一个小盒，所以事实是
the mechanism moving the way it does so
here's the strip I've made it's got a
移动就可以了
这就是展开的机制
here's the strip I've made it's got a
crease down the middle I'm going to glue
[音乐]
[掌声]
crease down the middle I'm going to glue
it in a minute
您
[音乐]
it in a minute
but first we'll just make a tab at one